

id             : 1d13af07-ea17-4927-94e7-37ec2f0c250d
request_type   : general_question
status         : answered
answer         : The HR helpdesk assistant can help with general HR questions, HR policy questions using supplied policy context, authorized 
                 employee-specific HR record lookups through approved tools, and HR ticket classification. It can also decline requests that are outside 
                 HR scope or that violate security rules.
requires_tool  : False
tool_name      : 
tool_arguments : 
category       : general_hr
priority       : low



